(Howard:)Are you saying
you want to get married?
(Penny:)Vegas isn't
that far away.
(Leonard:)I'm in. Let's do it.
(squeals quietly)
(Sheldon:)After all these years.
(Sheldon:)I'm really happy
for the two of you.
(Penny:)Oh, thank you.
Thanks.
(Sheldon:)Now get out of my spot.
(Howard:)Bernie, Stuart just pulled up.
(Howard:)So remember,
(Howard:)the key is to be firm.
(Howard:)Show no weakness.
(Sheldon:)Right.
Good luck.
(Bernadette:)Howard Joel Wolowitz,
you get back here.
(mutters) Never should have
told you my middle name.
(Stuart:)Hey, guys.
Hey, you got
a minute?
(Stuart:)Sure. Uh, let me just put
this stuff in the fridge.
(Stuart:)I felt bad for finishing
your yogurt, so I bought more.
And, Howard, your favorite
fruit is in season.
(Stuart:)Crunch Berries.